(soft music)
♪ Her hair is Harlow gold ♪
♪ Her lips a sweet surprise ♪
♪ Her hands are never cold ♪
♪ She's got Bette Davis eyes ♪
♪ She'll turn her music on you ♪
♪ You won't have
to think twice ♪
♪ She's pure as New York snow ♪
♪ She got Bette Davis eyes ♪
♪ And she'll tease you,
she'll unease you ♪
♪ All the better
just to please you ♪
♪ She's precocious, and
she knows just what it ♪
♪ Takes to make a pro blush ♪
♪ She got Greta Garbo's
standoff sighs ♪
♪ She's got Bette Davis eyes ♪
♪ She'll let you take her home ♪
♪ It whets her appetite ♪
♪ She'll lay you on a throne ♪
♪ She got Bette Davis eyes ♪
♪ She'll take a tumble on you ♪
♪ Roll you like you were dice ♪
♪ Until you come out blue ♪
♪ She's got Bette Davis eyes ♪
♪ She'll expose you,
when she snows you ♪
♪ Offer feed with the
crumbs she throws you ♪
♪ She's ferocious and
she knows just what it ♪
♪ Takes to make a pro blush ♪
♪ All the boys
think she's a spy,
she's got Bette Davis eyes ♪
♪♪♪
♪ And she'll tease you,
she'll unease you ♪
♪ All the better
just to please you ♪
♪ She's precocious, and
she knows just what it ♪
♪ Takes to make a pro blush ♪
♪ All the boys
think she's a spy,
she's got Bette Davis eyes ♪
♪♪♪
♪ She'll tease you ♪
♪ She'll unease you ♪
♪ Just to please you ♪
♪ She's got Bette Davis eyes ♪
♪ She'll expose you ♪
♪ When she snows you ♪
♪ 'Cause she knows you ♪